Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Here it crashes. down and crawls.
- And open the door fast and low.
- Hey. are you okay?
I'm sorry. I hadn't seen you leave.
Hey. let's go to the hospital the first...
I'm so sorry.
We should go to the hospital.
- Are you Korean?
- Yes.
Cut!
Tú vienes por aquí
y ya va el bastardo.
- Cut!
- See how it is now.
- Now it goes up.
From now on.
- He nailed it.
- Yes. to the fullest.
I'm sorry.
- Let's do it again!
- Cheer up! Cheer up!
They are all here. Turn and directly. pum.
But. if it gives me here.
anyway. at this distance.
I have to walk a few other
steps after the dialogue.
He departs here.
stops here and revolves here quickly.
From here it is more comfortable.
Enter here. then comes the bastard's car
and director Han's group is surrounded.
Another car comes and Han's group departs.
Wait!
Shit.
It's very hot to run so much.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org